No!
（潤平）チーって！
まあッ！
Goodness!
No, this is...
あッ　いや　これは…
That's what I lost in the locker room.
（楓）それ　更衣室から　なくなった
私の…
My—
My br—
ああ～
下…
M-My br—
下着！
My bra!
ダア～　水野さん　水野さーん！
Mizuno-san! Mizuno-san!
（千鶴）しかたないわよ
お年頃だものッ
You can't help it.
You're at that age!
≪（通行人Ａ）お年頃だもの
I'm at that age!
≪（Ｂ）でも　いけないことだよね
≪（Ｃ）下着をね…
But you still shouldn't do it, right?
An underwear thief...
俺　終了のお知らせ…
This is the end for me.
ano sora e kimi to hashiri dasou
I'll dash towards the sky.
negaigoto zenbu kanaete ageru...
I'll make all your wishes come true.
areya koreya to oshiyosete
Troubles engulfed me at every turn,
itsuno manika nichijou goodbye
and my normal days were gone before I knew it.
anote konote neko tedasuke
I help the cats with this and that.
guruguru mawaru triangle
The triangle whirls around me.
ukauka shite rarenai
There's no time to waste.
isoganakya ikenaitte
I'd better hurry.
kimi eno omoi mo sou nandaka karamawari de
My feelings towards you are spinning in circles.
tsuite nai koto mo
An unfortunate event
ookina chance ni naru kamo shirenai!
might prove to be a big opportunity!
kimi no egao ga mireta nara kitto
If I get to see your smile,
nyan toka narutte mae wo mukeru yo
I'll try to believe everything will be fine.
masa ni nyanderful
It's really a wonderful cat power.
itsuka kono te todokimasu you ni
May this hand reach you some day.
negaigoto zenbu kanaete miseru yo
I'll really make all your wishes come true.
Cat 08!
The Burning Private Instruction Runner
〈あのとき…　輝かしい未来に
向かっていた　あのとき〉
Back then,
when my life was still moving towards a bright future,
〈俺は　あんな悲劇が
待ち受けていたなんて〉
I could never have imagined that tragedy lay ahead.
〈想像だにしていなかった〉
ただいま～
I'm home.
（鈴）お帰りなさい　潤平兄ちゃん
（母）お帰り
Welcome home, Junpei.
Welcome home.
（ニャムサス）お帰り
（タマ）ダンナ　お帰り～
Master, welcome home.
Welcome home.
≪（ノワール）お帰りなさ～い
（琴音）遅かったわね　あなた
You were out late, dear.
（朱莉）おか…　えり
Welcome...
home.
…て　誰が　「あなた」だ
Who are you calling "dear"?!
ていうか　何で　お前らがウチに？
…アレルゲンだらけだし
Besides, why are you here?
And the place is full of allergens!
≪（ミッチー）汚いなあ
Yuck.
〈知らない猫〉
A cat I don't know...
What's wrong with my son?
ヤダねえ　この子は
わざわざ　遊びにきてくれたのに
They came all the way here to see you, and you just stand there embarrassed.
テレちゃって
テレてねえ！
I'm not embarrassed!
Kotone-chan, would you like more tea?
（母）琴音ちゃん
お茶のお代わりは？
いただきま～す
Thank you.
Akari-san, would you like another piece of cake?
（鈴）朱莉さん
ケーキ　もう１つ　どうです？
ありがとう　鈴ちゃん
Thank you, Suzu-chan.
Man, they've already made friends.
わあ～　なじんでる～
Don't be shy.
（母）遠慮しなくていいのよ
自分のウチだと思っていいからね
Make yourselves at home.
Yes, Mother.
は～い　お母さま
Oh my!
（母）まあ　娘が増えたみたいで
うれしいわ
This feels like I have more daughters! How marvelous!
本当に
増えるかもしれませんよ
Maybe you really will have more daughters.
Because...
だって　先輩とは
将来の約束が…
Senpai already made me a promise about the future.
そうだったの！？
そうだったの
Did you really?!
Are you serious?!
Wait a sec!
ちょっと待てい！
私も　お姉ちゃんが　ほしかったの
I've always wanted an older sister!
And I've wanted a little sister.
私も妹が　ほしくて
あたしが
いるでしょうが！
You have me!
え～い　ちょっと来い　お前ら！
Damn it! Come with me!
キャッ　手を…
（鈴）潤平兄ちゃん
Oh!
Junpei?
Junpei!
潤平…
キャ～
Jun—
ニャオ…
Wh-What are you doing?! Let go of us!
（朱莉）ちょっと何　離しなさいよ
いいから来い
Just come with me!
What's with that attitude?
何　その態度　せっかく困ってる猫
連れてきたのに　離してってば～
We're doing you a favor by bringing you a cat in need!
Let go of us!
No, don't let go of me ever.
いえ
ずっと離さなくても　いいです
Junpei-kun, you're rather forceful.
（千鶴）潤平くん　結構　強引なのね
Yeah, a boy needs to push his way through when it's time!
そうよね　男の子は
いくときは　いかなくっちゃ　ウフフフ
Faito ippatsu!
Note: A phrase used in commercials for a Japanese strength tonic. "Ippatsu" can also mean sex.
ファイト　いっぱーつ！
Oh my, ippatsu...
イヤ…　「いっぱつ」だなんて
So you want me to train you?
それで　この俺に　鍛えろと？
（ミッチー）そうです　ミッチー
スズメを捕れるように　なりたいです
Yes.
I want to be able to catch sparrows.
I have no stamina or athletic ability, so I can't catch them.
ミッチー　体力も運動神経もなくて
スズメを捕まえられなくて～
じゃあ　お前らが教えてやれば？
Then why don't you teach him?
そッ　それは
ダンナの大切な使命でさあ
Th-This is your important responsibility.
（ノワール）呪いを解きたいんでしょ？
You want to lift your curse, don't you?
Or do you want to turn into a cat?
それとも
猫になりたいのかい？
Is he that out of shape?
そんなにヒドイのか　コイツは…
Yeah.
何とかして
やんなさいよ
You should help him.
Senpai also looks nice when he's troubled.
困ってる先輩も
ステキ
やれやれ…　じゃ　やってみろよ
Man...
Then try it once.
（ミッチー）えッ？
あれ
Over there.
（一同）あれ？
Over there?
There?
はれ？
Go.
ほれ
（ミッチー）はいなッ
Okay!
ニャッ　ニャッ
ニャンセ　ニャン…
ニャ～ン　ニャ～ン…
See?
Don't give me that crap!
何が　「ねッ」だ～
（タマ）コイツは無理でさあ
（ニャムサス）現代っ子は　モヤシっ子だねえ
He's hopeless.
Kids these days are so weak.
He's more pathetic than Tama.
（ノワール）タマより情けないわね
ニャン！
それ　どういう意味でさあ
What's that supposed to mean?!
（ノワール）どうもこうも　ないわよ　フンッ
Don't you get it?
どタマ！
Piss off!
（タマ）どうするんでさあ
（ノワール）どうするのよ
What should we do?
What are you going to do?
What's your plan?
（ニャムサス）どうするつもりだい？
わかった…
All right, all right.
何とか　してやっか
ニャニャ！？　じゃあ
I guess I'll help.
Th-Then...
ありがとうございます　潤平さん
ミッチー　うれしいです～
Th-Thank you so much, Junpei-san!
I'm so happy!
Don't cling to me!
くっつくな！
感謝です～
Thank you!
Good for you.
（猫達・朱莉）よかったね
Also, you're having red bean rice and red snapper for dinner tonight, apparently.
それに今夜は　お赤飯と
鯛の尾頭付きとのことです
みんなで　お祝いしましょ
Let's celebrate together.
先ほど　お母さまと鈴ちゃんが
目を離しているスキに
While your mother and Suzu-chan weren't watching, I bugged your house.
盗聴器を
仕掛けさせていただきました
Don't do that!
仕掛けるな！
そうよ　ダメって言ったでしょ
Yeah! I told you not to!
盗聴は　二十歳になってから
You shouldn't eavesdrop until you've turned 21.
No, never.
I'm only joking.
冗談です
家族が増えるなら
増築しないと　狭いわよねえ
If we're getting more family members, we'll need more room.
思い切って
二世帯住宅にしちゃう？
Should we go for a big change and buy a duplex?
Was she really joking?
〈ホントに冗談なんだろうな〉
≪（ミッチー）ヒ～ヒ～
もうダメです
I can't go on.
Don't stop there, weakling!
おい　止まるな　貧弱な坊や！
We haven't even run for a minute yet!
まだ１分も　走ってねえぞ
この声…
Is that voice...
Sheesh.
まったく
ヒ～ヒ～…
Plea... let me... rest...
ミッチー　こッ　呼吸が…
高坂く～ん
Kousaka-kun!
M-Mizuno!
みッ　水野　隠れろ！
は　はい
Hide!
Y-Yes.
おはよ～う
高坂くんもジョギング？
Good morning!
Are you jogging too?
お　おお…
誰か一緒だった？
Y-Yeah.
Were you with someone else?
なッ　何で？
Wh-Why?
You were saying, "Don't stop there, weakling!"
今　「おい　止まるな
貧弱な坊や！」って
Oh, th-that was...
いや　そッ　その…
自分に言い聞かせてたんだ
I was talking to myself.
"You're out of shape and weak, so get strong!" See?
運動不足だし　貧弱だから
「走れ！　鍛えろ！」ってね
You're not that weak.
高坂くん　別に貧弱じゃないよ
えッ？　…あッ
水野…
高坂くん…
Mizuno...
Kousaka-kun...
Kaede...
≪（凪）楓→
ハッハッハッ　偶然だなあ
What a coincidence, huh?
You're training in the morning, even after the track meet?
大会が終わったのに　朝練とは
感心　感心
Very good.
I know what you're doing.
わかるぞ
なッ　何が？
Wh-What?
You're training to become a man suitable for me both physically and mentally.
つまり　体を鍛えて
身も心も　私に　ふさわしい男に
なろうというのだな
いや　違います
Not really.
Man, you're good at knocking me over.
まったく　この腰砕き上手め
すみません
Sorry.
うん？
まあ　いいさ
That's okay.
とにかく　今日の放課後から
Anyway, starting after school today,
come to the track team's rookie tryouts!
陸上部に体験入部　決定～！
ええーッ
And!
さら～に　体験入部するからには
If you come to the tryouts, you'd better cross the love-love finish line with Kaede,
ラブラブ一直線で
楓と　愛のゴールテープを切らないと
即　私と結納ッ！
な～ぜに！
or you'll have to marry me at once!
Why?!
（凪）お～い　楓　いい話があるぞ～
Hey Kaede, I have good news.
は～い　何ですか～
Coming! What is it?
Junpei-san, did you forget about me?
潤平さん
ミッチーを忘れてませんか？
Marriage! Marriage!
（凪）ゆいのう　ゆいのう…
Marriage!
So... don't the rookies disturb your training?
あの　体験入部って
ジャマじゃないんですか？
Marriage! Marriage! Marriage!
かまわん　今の時期は　主に
基礎練習とトレーニングだからな
It's perfectly all right.
At this time of year, we're just working on conditioning.
お待たせしました
（加奈子）お待た
Thank you for waiting!
Hey!
あッ　住吉！？
Sumiyoshi?
I told her about the tryouts,
and she said she wanted to come too.
体験入部の話をしたら
カナちゃんも　やりたいって
I'm way out of shape.
あたしも　最近
スッゲー運動不足でさあ
Let's do it together, Junpei, Nagi-senpai.
よろしくな　潤平　ナギー先輩
う～ん　１年３６５日　２４時間
けしからん乳だ
These boobs are unforgivable 24/7, 365 days a year.
This is getting old.
ワンパターンでっせ
何すんねん　加奈子
Stop it, Kanako!
それは　こっちのセリフや
この～
Same to you!
Stop, Kana-chan, Senpai!
あの～　カナちゃん　先輩！
Kaede!
楓！　私は乳を見てるから…
I'll be watching those boobs...
I mean,
ううん　もとーい
他の部員を見てるから～
I'll be watching the other members, so you coach these two!
この２人の指導は　楓がするよ～に
はいッ
Yes!
頼んだぞ！
I'm counting on you!
Here it comes!
そ～れいッ
…て　なぜ　テニス？
Why tennis?!
I'm their helper!
助っ人だよ　助っ人！
頼まれちゃって
They asked me.
…て　なぜ　バスケ？
Why basketball?
I'm their helper!
助っ人だよ　助っ人　頼まれて
They asked me.
…て　なぜ　ソフト？
助っ人だよ　助っ人～
Why softball?
Batter: Mizuno
I'm their helper!
…て　なぜ　卓球？
助っ人だよ　助っ人
Why ping-pong?
I'm their helper!
And sumo.
相撲も　スイミングも
And swimming.
バレーも　シンクロも
And volleyball.
And synchronized swimming.
み～んな　助っ人
I'm helping everyone.
ああ　しんど…
I'm dead.
カナちゃん　汗　かくから
Kana-chan, we sweat a lot, so you should bring a change of underwear tomorrow.
明日　替えの下着
用意しておいた方が　いいよ
ああ　下着ね　わかった
Yeah, underwear...
All right.
カナちゃん　大丈夫？
Are you all right, Kana-chan?
He's not coming.
≪（ミッチー）来ませんね～→
もう夜ですよ　潤平さん
It's already dark, Junpei-san.
星が　キレイだ～
The stars are so pretty.
お父さんは？
お父さんは　帰ってこないわ
Hey, where's Dad?
He's not coming home.
父さん
高坂家の安全は…　心配！
Dad, the safety of the Kousaka family is...
in danger!
That was terrible!
もう　ヒドイです
ミッチー　待ちぼうけですよ！
I waited here the whole time!
I totally forgot. Sorry.
忘れてて悪かったよ
反省してください
You'd better be sorry!
Kousaka-kun!
高坂く～ん　オス！
Hey!
オ　オッ　オス！
H-H-Hey!
今度
柔道部の助っ人も頼まれちゃった
The judo club asked me to help them too.
どうかなあ　似合う？
What do you think?
Does it look good on me?
似合う　似合う
水野に　投げられたいくらいだよ
It does!
I want you to throw me.
Seoi-nage!
背負い投げ
うわ～
あの～
Um...
はッ
汗　かいてるよ
You're sweating.
〈み　み　水野…〉
M-M-Mizuno...
〈み　み　み…〉
M-M-M-M-Mi—
何？
カナちゃんからだ
What is it?
It's from Kana-chan.
えっと　「今日は筋肉痛だから
学校は　お休みします」って
Let's see...
"My muscles are really sore, so I'm not coming to school today."
そッ　そうか
ヤワだな　アイツも
R-Really.
She's so fragile.
ああ…
ハンカチ　洗って返すよ
Oh, I'll wash your handkerchief before returning it.
あッ　いいよ　そんなの
Don't worry about it.
R-R-Really, I'll wash it.
いい…　洗う　洗う
あッ　でも
But...
I'll wash it.
ム～ッ　ム～ニュグ！
女物よね
女物…　じゃ　琴音さんの？
Isn't that a girl's design?
It is.
So, is it Kotone-san's?
朱莉ちゃんの？
Or Akari-chan's?
He's their slave already?
もう　尻に敷かれてるのかい
Bye!
じゃあね　また明日
See you tomorrow!
≪目標を確認
Target confirmed.
ニャイヤリ
ニャッ！　ニャヒ～…
ニャ～
Oh?
あら？
（陸上部員Ａ）どっから来たんだ？
Where did you come from?
He's cute!
（Ｂ）カワイイ～
猫ちゃん　どうしたの？
What's the matter, kitty?
ニャ～ン　ニャ～ン
≪（凪）陸上部　集合！
Track club, gather around!
Oh, we're starting!
あッ　始まるよ
みんな　行きましょう
Let's go, everyone.
Yes!
（３人）はいッ
ニャン
ニャヒッ
（晴彦）はッ
Hurry!
（女子生徒Ａ）早く　早く
（Ｂ）もう　追いついてる
But I've caught up to you!
Yeah! Yeah!
そうよ　俺も予約しておいたギャルゲー
「もえにゃん」　取りに行かないと→
I need to go pick up the new gal game, "Moe-nyan"!
Tonight's going to be maid night!
今夜は朝まで　ミッドナ～イト
We'll run five laps after stretching.
はい
柔軟　終わったら　トラック５周
Manager, keep time for us.
マネージャーは　タイム　測って
〈水野って　こんなビシッとした
一面もあるんだ〉
Mizuno can be very forceful too.
はいッ
Kousaka-kun, don't force yourself to swing your arms. Just relax.
高坂くん　腕を振るとき
力を入れずに　自然な感じに
And you'll find it easier to breath from your belly.
それに
おなかで呼吸すると　楽だよ
Like this.
ハッハッて
I see!
なるほど　水野　教え上手だな
You're good at coaching!
Not really.
そんなことないよ
ああッ
Mizuno! Mizuno!
水野　水野～ッ
フフフ…　いい気になってるのも
今のうちですよ
Your fun times will soon be over.
All right, we'll call it a day.
（凪）はい　では今日は　ここまで
（一同）お疲れさまでした！
Good work!
Huh?
あれ？
どうした　楓？
What's wrong, Kaede?
My bra...
その　下着が…
下着！？
Your bra?
No, it's nothing.
いえ　何でもありません
I guess I forgot my spare one.
〈きっと　替えの下着
忘れてきちゃったんだ〉
Were you waiting long?
待った～？
水野　どうしたの？
Mizuno! What happened?
Sorry, I had a minor issue.
ごめんね　ちょっと　あって
Anyway, how are you doing?
それより　高坂くん　どう？
つらくない？
Can you keep up?
Yeah. I have some sore muscles, but I'm fine.
ああ　少し筋肉痛だけど　平気
寝る前に
マッサージした方が　いいよ
You need to massage them before you go to sleep.
In the bath too.
それと　お風呂でもね
Yeah.
うん　ああ　そうだ　水野
By the way, Mizuno...
何？
Yes?
I need to return your handkerchief.
ハンカチ　返さないと
You can take your time.
いつでも　よかったのに
I washed it and ironed it too.
ちゃんと　洗って
アイロン　かけてきたんだ　はい
Here's your handkerchi—
ハンカ…　うん？
Chi?
No...
チッ　チーって！
No!
Goodness!
まあッ！
あッ　いや　これは…
No, this is...
That's what I lost in the locker room.
それ　更衣室から　なくなった
私の…
My—
My br—
M-My br—
ああ～
下…
My bra!
下着！
ダア～　水野さん　水野さーん！
Mizuno-san! Mizuno-san!
しかたないわよ　お年頃だものッ
You can't help it.
You're at that age!
≪（通行人Ａ）お年頃だもの
I'm at that age!
≪（Ｂ）でも　いけないことだよね
But you still shouldn't do it, right?
≪（Ｃ）下着をね…
An underwear thief...
This is the end for me.
俺　終了のお知らせ…
水野…　来てるわけねえよな
Mizuno... obviously she's not coming.
Damn it! Mitch! That's...
おい　ミッチー　それ！
お前の仕業かあッ！
Was this your doing?!
ええ　ミッチーが　やったのです
It was.
何で！？　せっかく水野と
いいムードだったのに
Why?!
I was doing just great with Mizuno!
これじゃ　台なしじゃねえかよ！
You've ruined everything!
いい気味ですよ
Serves you right.
What have I done to you?!
てめえ　何の恨みがあって！
何だよ
潤平さんが　悪いんですよ
What?
It's all your fault.
俺が？
ミッチーを　ほうっておいて
Mine?
You abandoned me to spend time with a girl!
自分ばっかり　いい感じになって
いい感じ？　お前　何を…
A girl?
What are you...
だから　だから　ミッチーだって
Because...
Because I want to get close to Su-chan!
スーちゃんと仲よく　なりたいのに
スーちゃんと　いい感じになりたい
って言ってるんです
I want to be lovey-dovey with Su-chan!
どういうことだ？
だから　ミッチーだって！
And what does that mean?
I want to!
《スーちゃん
ミッチーと　つきあってください》
Su-chan, would you go out with me?
I won't consider a weakling who can't even catch a sparrow.
《（スーちゃん）あたし
スズメも捕れない貧弱な坊やは　イヤ→》
《スズメを捕れるようになったら
また考えてあげても　いいわ…》
I may change my mind if you catch one.
I may.
《ウソ～！》
But I'm a weakling.
〈（ミッチー）でも　ミッチーは
貧弱な坊やなんだ〉
潤平さんが　協力してくれれば
If you help me, maybe I can get together with Su-chan.
スーちゃんと
うまく　いけるかもしれないのに
潤平さんは
自分ばっかり　幸せになって
But you're only making yourself happy!
Mitch...
ミッチー
ヤキモチ焼いたって　いいじゃないか
Can you blame me for being jealous?!
I'm just a weakling!
だって　猫だもの～
Ｂｙ　ミッチー
I am!
「だもの」は　ともかく
それは　すまなかった
Well... sorry.
潤平さん…
Junpei-san...
お前の言うとおりだ　頑張ろう
You're right.
Let's work together, so you can go out with Su-chan.
スーちゃんと　うまく　いくように
Junpei-san!
潤平さん…
すみませんでした　下着のこと
I'm sorry about the bra.
いいよ
終わったし　いろんな意味で
It's okay.
It's all over, in every sense.
そんな暗い顔しないでください
Don't be so depressed.
潤平さんと　あのキレイな女の人
You and that lovely girl looked good together.
とっても　お似合いでしたよ
そッ　そうか？
そうですよ
R-Really?
You did!
だから
きっと　誤解は解けますって
So I'm sure you can clear up this misunderstanding.
そうか…　なら　いいけど
Yeah?
I hope so.
だって　誤解なんですから
Because it's really only a misunderstanding.
Yeah!
そうだよなあ　誤解なんだもんな！
It's only a misunderstanding!
はい　ミッチーが保証しますよ
Yeah! I guarantee it!
この誤解は　必ず解けるって
You can clear up this misunderstanding!
Yeah!
おおッ
何とかなる気がしてきたぜ
I'm starting to feel like it'll work out!
いよッ　大統領
ニクイね　この！　アハハ…
Yeah! You're great! Leader!
それじゃ　スズメを捕れるように
Now, I'll train you hard so you can catch a sparrow!
お前を　徹底的に鍛えてやる～ッ
いいな！
Ready?!
Yeah!
アア～ウ
ちょっと待て
もう少し　ゆっくり走ってくれ～
Wait! Wait up!
Slow down a little!
≪（鈴）行ってきま～す
Bye!
M-Mitch!
ミッ　ミッチー
Junpei-san, thank you for everything.
（ミッチー）潤平さん
いろいろ　ありがとうございました
（ニャムサス）もう誰も　お前を
貧弱な坊やとは呼ばないだろうさ
Nobody will call you a weakling anymore.
（タマ）立派なオスに　なりやしたね
You've become a great feline.
フッ…
それでは　これからスズメを捕って
I'll go catch a sparrow, and then I'll ask Su-chan out again.
もう一度
スーちゃんに　アタックです
Good luck.
頑張れよ
（ミッチー）では　行ってきます→
Here I go.
フッ　フッ　ハアッ
Kousaka?
高坂？
アイツなら　今朝も走っていたぞ
He was jogging again this morning.
You're not jogging, Kaede?
楓は最近　走ってないのか？
D-Did something happen?
何か　あったのか？
あッ　いえ　何でも…
No, nothing happened.
…て　それ　私の
あッ
That's mine.
楓…
変なこと聞くようですけど
Kaede!
Um, this might sound weird, but...
大丈夫だ　もう慣れてる
Don't worry, I'm used to it.
この間　部室のロッカーから
替えの下着が　なくなったの…
My bra went missing from my locker the other day.
ああッ
それは見つかったんですけど
Oh, I already found it, but...
男の子って　女の子の下着に
興味が　あるものなのかな
Are all boys interested in girls underwear?
男の子！？
下着！？
Boys?!
Underwear?!
Junpei!
≪デジャブ～
Déjà vu.
何だ？
What the heck?
（凪）高坂ーッ
（加奈子）潤平ーッ
Kousaka!
Junpei, damn you!
痛ッ
高坂！
Ow...
Kousaka!
Junpei!
潤平ッ　楓の下着を盗んだってのは
どういうことだ！
Why did you steal Kaede's bra?!
（晃太）盗んじゃったのか？
あらら
He stole it?
Oh my...
Why didn't you steal mine?!
（凪）どうして
私の下着を盗まないのだ！
W-Wait! Sumiyoshi! Nagi-senpai!
ちょッ　ちょっと　住吉　ナギー先輩
この　ド変態！
言ってくれれば　いつでも　やるぞ
You damn perv!
Just say the word, and you can have mine anytime!
…て　誤解だよ　誤解
It's all a misunderstanding!
あれは　ミッチー
いや　猫が　俺のカバンの中に
It was Mitch...
I mean, a cat put it in my bag!
ふかしこくんじゃねえ！
猫が下着　盗んだりするもんかッ
Stop lying!
A cat wouldn't steal underwear!
（凪）高坂潤平　さすがに
その言い訳は　苦しいぞ！
Kousaka Junpei!
That excuse is way too lame!
I-It's the truth!
ほッ　本当のことだ～ッ
ノット　ギルティー
I'm not guilty!
So, you're saying a cat took the bra...
ほお～
それじゃ　猫が女子更衣室から
男子更衣室に
下着を持っていったというんだな
...from the girls locker room to the boys?
苦しい　苦しい
That's so lame.
But still, it really happened!
んなこと言われても　ホントに
そうなんだから　しかたねえだろ
あッ
（一同）何だ？
What?
I saw it.
（晴彦）俺　見た
（一同）何を？
Saw what?
A cat with some underwear in its mouth...
≪（晴彦）下着　くわえたドラ猫が→
walked from the girls locker room to the boys.
女子更衣室から　男子更衣室に
入っていくの
えッ？
いや～　最近の猫は
It made me think, "Man, cats these days carry not just fish, but bras too!"
お魚だけじゃなくて　いろいろな物
くわえるんだなあって
はだしで　ゆかいに
追いかけたりは　しなかったけどね
I didn't make a scene chasing it on bare feet, though.
な～んだ　猫の仕業だったのか
Oh, a cat did it.
では　しかたあるまい
Then we can't blame anyone.
（晃太）疑いが晴れて
（一同）よかった　よかった
Now that this mystery is solved...
It's all good!
カナちゃん　先輩！
Kana-chan! Senpai!
Don't worry.
安心しな
誤解は　すべて解けた
All doubt has been removed.
えッ？
潤平が盗んでなかったってこと
Junpei didn't steal your bra.
えッ…　誤解？
So it was a misunderstanding?
Anyway, I'm thinking about setting up a camera next time.
（琴音）だから　今度は
カメラを付けようと思うの
でも　高坂先輩　イヤがるかしら
But won't that annoy Kousaka-senpai?
そりゃ～　イヤがるわよ
Of course it will.
But... I can't wait to see Kousaka-senpai looking annoyed.
でも　イヤがってる高坂先輩の顔…
た・の・し・み
…て　琴音ちゃん
盗撮は　二十歳になってから！
Kotone-chan, don't use spy cams before you've turned 21.
冗談よ
I'm only joking.
Say no to voyeurism
Was that really only a joke?
本当に　冗談なんでしょうねえ
うん
Yeah,
（琴音）冗談だよ
it's a joke.
えッ　じゃあ
猫ちゃんのイタズラ？
So the kitty pulled a prank?
ああ　それで
ごめんなさい
Yeah, so...
I'm sorry!
それなのに　私が誤解しちゃって
I was too hasty and misunderstood.
いや　俺の方こそ
I'm sorry too.
ごめん
あの…
何？
Hey...
What?
また…
うん？
Can...
また　今度…
えッ？
Can we...
また　今度
あッ　もう　こんな時間
Can we—
It's so late already!
私　部活に行かなくちゃ
I need to go to practice!
あッ　水野！
あッ…
Mizuno!
何？
ハンカ…
Yes?
The handker—
あッ　あの…　ちゃんと洗って
I washed it and ironed it too.
アイロン　かけてきたんだよ
ありがとう
Thank you.
ああ…
じゃあ　また明日
See you tomorrow.
Yeah.
Yeah!
Junpei-san, it's your turn to give it a shot.
〈（ミッチー）潤平さん
今度は　アンタが頑張る番だぜ〉
（凪）遅いぞ　楓
（陸上部員）早く　早く
You're late, Kaede!
Hurry! Hurry!
（スーちゃん）ウッフ　ステキよ　ミッチー
You're so wonderful, Mitch.
Yeah.
〈（ミッチー）今度は　お前の男を→〉
It's your turn now...
〈見せてみな〉
to be a man.
水野の俊足は　幼い頃より　日夜
犬の散歩に励んできたタマモノ
natsu no kaze kirameku machi ni
In this town where the wind sparkles,
nigemizu oikakeru anata no sugata
I see you chasing a mirage.
shinkokyuu shite oikakeru kedo
You take a deep breath and keep chasing it.
chiisaku kieteyuku senaka ni sotto tsubuyaita
I whisper to your back as you get further away.
nemurenai yoru ni me wo tojite
When I close my eyes on sleepless nights,
omoiegaku mirai niwa
and imagine my future,
futari no egao sore igai ni mou mienai
I can only see the two of us smiling together.
konnani setsunai kimochi
This really sweet, painful thought...
kizuite kurenakutemo
Even if you never notice it,
kokoro ni sotto negau dake
I just wish for it in my mind.
ashita ni nareba kanau hazu!
I'm sure it'll come true tomorrow!
surechigatta shunkan ni
At the moment we passed by each other,
waraikakete kureta ne
you gave me a smile.
soredake de mune ga atsui
Just that makes my heart glow,
shiawase dakara
because I'm happy...
because I'm happy.
Strawberry Tears
Strawberry tears.
Today's Nyan Koma.
Today's Mew view
Mizuno's running ability is probably the result of her walking her dogs every day since childhood.
どうしたのかな
みんな　今日は元気ないぞ～
What's wrong with you guys?
You're slower than normal.
まあ　鍛え方が違うっつーか
She's in a totally different dimension.
（晴彦）ギャルゲーの限定版が売り切れる
（母・鈴）スーパーのサービスタイムが～
The new gal game will be sold out soon!
A super sale at the supermarket!
（住職）嬢との待ち合わせが
（一ノ瀬家・舎弟）凪お嬢さま～
I'm late for a date!
Lady Nagi!
常盤町
そこは　過酷なワイルドタウン
Tokiwa-cho... it's a cruel and wild town.
Mew view
ちなみに　猫の最高速度は
時速４０キロオーバーらしいよ
By the way, cats can reach a top speed of more than 40 km/h.
Now, the next Nyan Koi...
Second semester final exam last-minute study session...
in the pool!
What?!
Junpei, what do you think of this swimsuit?
Mizuno, it looks good on you.
Thank you.
You too.
Next Nyan Koi, 9th nyan-ko, "Girls in the Water!".
Junpei, you were just talking with a cat.
Crap, did she find about the curse?
Do you like... know what cats think?
Y-Yeah! I guess!